Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - New York State: Governor, 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - New York State: Governor, 1959-1971 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - New York State: Governor, 1959-1971 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - New York State: Governor, 1959-1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - New York State: Infrastructure, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - New York State: Infrastructure, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - New York State: NYS Mediation Board, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - New York State: Leg. Comm. on Pubic-Private Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - New York State: Leg. Comm. on Pubic-Private Cooperation, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - New York State: Senate, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - New York State: Taxes, 1960-1964 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - New York State: Transportation, 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - New York State: Transportation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Occupational Safety, 1948; 1957-1962 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Occupational Safety, 1940-1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Occupational Safety, 1950-1959 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Occupational Safety, 1968-1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Occupational Safety, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Occupational Safety, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Occupational Safety, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Occupational Safety, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Occupational Safety, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Occupational Safety, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Occupational Safety, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Occupational Safety, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Occupational Safety, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Occupational Safety: NYS Occ. Safety & Health Councils, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Occupational Safety: OSH Labor Management Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Occupational Safety: Universities OSH Education Resource Center, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Occupational Safety: NYS AFL-CIO Statements, 1960-1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Occupational Safety: Boiler Safety Regulations, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Occupational Safety: Boiler Safety Regulations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Occupational Safety: Boiler Safety Regulations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Occupational Safety: Boiler Safety Regulations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Occupational Safety: Boiler Safety Regulations, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Patronage, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pension Plans: Reports and Pamphlets, 1950-1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pension Plans: NYS AFL-CIO Plan, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Plant Closings, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Political Campaigns, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Political Parties: General, 1950-1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Political Parties: Democratic Party, 1956-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Political Parties: Democratic Party, 1958-1976 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Political Parties: Republican Party, 1952-1958 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Political Parties: Socialist Party 1956 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Press, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Product Liability, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Public Employees: Condin Wadlin Law, 1957-1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Public Employees: Taylor Law, 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Public Employees: Statements, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Public Employees: Statements, 1960-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Public Employees: Statements, 1978-1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Public Employees: Conference, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Public Employees: Reports, 1966-1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Public Power, 1966-1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Public Power, 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Railroads: General, 1959-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: Clippings, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: Feather-bedding, 1959-1962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Full Crew Laws, 1960-1961 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Railroads: Full Crew Laws, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Railroads: Mergers, 1961-1966 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Railroads: Mergers, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Regulatory Reform, 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rent Control: NYCIO position, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Right-to-Work Laws: Pamphlets, PR material, 1950-1959 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Right-to-Work Laws: Pamphlets, PR material, 1960-1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Right-to-Work Laws: Taft-Hartley, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Right-to-Work Laws: Union Materials, 1947-1969 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Right-to-Work Laws: Non-Union Materials, 1949-1966 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Social Security, 1967-1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Socialism, 1950-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Strikes: General, 1950-1969 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Strikes: Steel Strike, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Strikes: Strikebreaking, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Strikes: Welfare Benefits for Strikers, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Taxes, 1975-1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment, 1940; 1959-1982 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1946; 1950-1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Hughes-Ashberry Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Hughes-Ashberry Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Hughes-Ashberry Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Hughes-Ashberry Bill, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Unemployment Insurance: ILGWU, 1970-1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Laws compared by state, 1962-1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Lawsuits, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment Insurance: Committee, 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Unions: General, 1951-1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Unions: Controls, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Unions: Health & Welfare, 1949-1951 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Unions: International, 1956-1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Unions: Left, 1950-1952 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Unions: Publications, 1957-1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Unions: Amal. Clothing Workers of America, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Unions: International Chemical Workers, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Unions: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Unions: Newspaper Guild of New York, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Unions: Newspaper Guild of New York, 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Unions: Transit Workers of America, 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Unions: Union Label & Service Trades, 1954; 1957 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Unions: Union Label & Service Trade, 1960-1969 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - United Nations, 1950-1969 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Wages: General, 1957-1983 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Wages: Prevailing Wage, 1963-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Wages: Prevailing Wage, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wages: Prevailing Wage, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Wages: Prevailing Wage, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Welfare: 1950-1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Welfare: 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Welfare: 1970-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Welfare: 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Welfare: Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Welfare: Medical Services, 1966-1969; 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Welfare: Strikers Benefits, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Welfare: Work Incentives, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Women Workers: 1956, 1960-1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Women Workers: 1969 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Women Workers: 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Women Workers: 1973-1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Women Workers: AFL-CIO Womens Auxiliaries, 1950-1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Women Workers: Lawsuit 1973-1974 re. Pregnancy/Disability Benefits (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Work Hours, 1956-1964 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Workers Comp: 1957 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Workers Comp: 1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Workers Comp: 1959 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Workers Comp: 1960 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Workers Comp: 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Workers Comp: 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Workers Comp: 1966-1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Workers Comp: 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Workers Comp: 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Workers Comp: 1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Workers Comp: 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Workers Comp: 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Workers Comp: 1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Workers Comp: 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Workers Comp: 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Workers Comp: 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Workers Comp: 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Workers Comp: 1980 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Workers Comp: 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Workers Comp: 1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Workers Comp: Aggregate Trust Fund, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Workers Comp: Aggregate Trust Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Workers Comp: Aggregate Trust Fund, 1973-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Workers Comp: Aggregate Trust Fund, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Workers Comp: Committee, 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Workers Comp: Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Workers Comp: Committee, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Workers Comp: Correspondence, 1966-1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1950-1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1956-1959 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1960-1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1970-1979 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits 1980-1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits, Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits, Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits, Statement, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Workers Comp: Disability Benefits Studies, Mar-83 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Workers Comp: Insurance Rates, 1969-1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Workers Comp: Insurance Rates, 1978-1981 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Workers Comp: Insurance Rates, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Workers Comp: Offset, 1963-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Workers Comp: Out-of-State, 1960-1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Workers Comp: Out-of-State, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Workers Comp: Publications NYCIO, 1950-1958 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Workers Comp: Publications NYS, 1950-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Workers Comp: Publications NYS, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Workers Comp: Rehabilitation, 1956-1958 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Workers Comp: Rehabilitation, 1960-1961 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Workers Comp: Rehabilitation, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Workers Comp: Rehabilitation, Apr 25 1977 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Workers Comp: Rehabilitation, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Workers Comp: State Insurance Fund, 1949-1965 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Workers Comp: State University Construction Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - COPE: Proposed By-laws, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - COPE: Financial Report, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - COPE: Printed Materials, 1958-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Conventions: 1938 NYSFL (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Conventions: 1949-1950 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Conventions: 1950 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Conventions: 1951-1955 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Conventions: 1956 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Conventions: 1957 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Conventions: 1957 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Conventions: 1958 NYCIO (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Conventions: 1958 Merger Convention (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Conventions: 1959 Leg. Conference (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Conventions: 1959 COPE Conference (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Conventions: 1959 Annual Convention (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Conventions: 1960 Annual Convention (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Conventions: 1960 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Conventions: 1961 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Conventions: 1962 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Conventions: 1962 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Conventions: 1963 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Conventions: 1964 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Conventions: 1964 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Conventions: 1965 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Conventions: 1965 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Conventions: 1966 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Conventions: 1966 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Conventions: 1967 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Conventions: 1968 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Conventions: 1968 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Conventions: 1969 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Conventions: 1969 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Conventions: 1970 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Conventions: 1970 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Conventions: 1971 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Conventions: 1973 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Conventions: 1974 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Conventions: 1975 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Conventions: 1976 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Conventions: 1976 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Conventions: 1977 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Conventions: 1978 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Conventions: 1978 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Conventions: 1978 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Conventions: 1978 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Conventions: 1978 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Conventions: 1979 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Conventions: 1980 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Conventions: 1980 Annual Constitutioal Convention (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Conventions: 1980 Annual Constitutional Convention (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Conventions: 1981 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Conventions: 1982 Legislative Conference (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Conventions: 1982 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Corporate Documentations: NYS AFL-CIO Constitution, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Executive Council: Meeting material, 1959-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Executive Council: Membership, 1958-1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Executive Council: Resolutions, Statements, 1976-1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Positions: Endorsement memoranda, 1958-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Legislative Positions: Endorsement memoranda, Jan-May 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Legislative Positions: Endorsement memoranda, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Legislative Positions: Opposition memoranda, 1957-1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Legislative Positions: Opposition memoranda, Jan-May 1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Legislative Positions: Opposition memoranda, Jan-Jun 1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Program: 1951-1958 NYCIO (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Legislative Program: 1957-1958 NYSFL (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Program: 1963 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Legislative Program: 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Legislative Program: 1978 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Legislative Program: 1979 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Legislative Program: 1981 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Legislative Program: 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Membership Lists: 1956-1957 NYCIO (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Membership Lists: 1974 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Merger: Correspondence 1956-1958 NYSFL (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Merger: Correspondence 1956-1958 NYCIO (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Merger: Meetings, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Merger: Meetings, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Merger: Merger Agreement, Oct 29 1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Merger: Press release and clippings, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Merger: Resolutions, 1956-1958 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Merger: Statements, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Officers, RRC: Biographical Material, 1962; 1974 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Officers, RRC: COPE 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Officers, RRC: COPE 1974 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Officers, RRC: COPE 1974 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Officers, RRC: COPE 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Officers, RRC: Conferences, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Officers, RRC: Conferences, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence 1956-1966 in/out, 1959-1966 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jan-Sep 1969 in/out (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Oct-Dec 1969 in/out (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jan-Apr 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence 1971-1973 in/out (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jan 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Feb 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Mar 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Apr 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence May 1975 in/out (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jun 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jul 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Aug 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Sep 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Oct 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Nov 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Dec 1974 in/out (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence from NYS Federal Politicians, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence 1975 in/out (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jan-Aug 1976 in/out (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Sep-Dec 1976 in/out (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence Jan-Mar 1977 in/out (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence 1980 in/out (selected) (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Officers, RRC: Correspondence 1987-1982 in/out (selected), 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Officers, RRC: Memos, 1960-1969 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Officers, RRC: NYSFL 1948 Annual Convention (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Officers, RRC: NYSFL 1958 Dispute (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Officers, RRC: NYSFL 1958 Executive Council (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Officers, RRC: NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings 1960 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Officers, RRC: NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Officers, RRC: NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Officers, RRC: NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Officers, RRC: NYS AFL-CIO Executive Council Membership, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1958-1962 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1963 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1964 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1965 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1967 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1970-1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Officers, RRC: Speeches, Statements 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Binding Arbitration, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Commun. Workers of America, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Cuomo, Marion 1982 election (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Cuomo, Marion 1982 election (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Cuomo, Marion 1982 election (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Cuomo, Marion 1982 election, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Italian Earthquake Relief Fund, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Maritime Appropriations Bill, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Meany, George; Retirement, Death, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Officers, RRC Subjects: Occupational Safety, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Officers, Garno, Harold: Bio Material 1959 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Officers, Garno, Harold: Correspondence, memoranda, 1956-1962 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Officers, Garno, Harold: Statements 1955-1957 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Bio Material, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Memoranda, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Speeches, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Speeches 1960 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Officers, Hanover, Harold: Speeches 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: Biographical Material, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: COPE, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: COPE, 1960-1963 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: Correspondence, 1950; 1956-1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: Memos from LJ, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Officers, Hollander, Louis: Speeches, 1958-1961 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Officers, Jaffe, Ludwig (LJ): Biographical Material, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)